{
    "subject": "resource/Dynasty_(As_They_Sleep_album)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Album",
    "human_readable": "The Dynasty album is an album.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9661988615989685,
            "question": "Is 'The Dynasty' a song or an album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502219915390015,
            "question": "Are there any notable songs on the album 'The Dynasty'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7069134712219238,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the album 'The Dynasty'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4549959897994995,
            "question": "Who created or released 'The Dynasty'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4377537667751312,
            "question": "When was 'The Dynasty' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2057604044675827,
            "question": "What is the overall theme or concept of 'The Dynasty'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19602808356285095,
            "question": "Has 'The Dynasty' received any critical acclaim or awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19241510331630707,
            "question": "Does 'The Dynasty' belong to a specific genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15984877943992615,
            "question": "What type of work is 'The Dynasty'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10780217498540878,
            "question": "Where can I listen to or purchase 'The Dynasty'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Dynasty album is an album.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1712_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is 'The Dynasty'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1712_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'The Dynasty' belong to a specific genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1712_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'The Dynasty' received any critical acclaim or awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1712_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1712_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about various albums, including \"Dynasty,\" confirming that it is indeed an album. Therefore, the statement \"The Dynasty album is an album\" is correct according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}